

# **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

### CONTACT



lshybrohm@gmail.com



540 - 755 - 9885



/laura-shy



laurashy.github.io/portfolio-website/

#### WORK SKILLS

HTML CSS

Express

JavaScript

REST

Node.js

jQuery PostgreSQL

REACT

MongoDB

User Testing

TDD/BDD

API Integration

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit Quick Thinker Interpersonal Skills Reliable and professional Organized Time management Collaboration & communication Motivated

## TOOLS

Microsoft Word Microsoft PowerPoint Google Drawings Google Sheets Google Slides and Docs Slack Figma, Canva, and basic Adobe MAC & PC Systems Android & iOS Systems

## ABOUT

Full stack web developer with a strong background in project management, managing multiple concurrent tasks, and collaboration. Former educator experienced in analyzing a team to assess progress. procedures, and viable improvements to meet goals and ensure success, with a willingness to further develop their skills with the right team.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Website for Thrive Music Academy

AUG 2021

- · Guided the client through establishing a solid foundation for needs and wants of their website and business.
- Created a single-page website for a new business in the community using HTML and CSS
- · Produced flyers, logos, infographics, and a brochure, maximizing the client's marketing campaign

# Orchestra Director, HCPS and FCPS JUN 2016 - AUG 2021

- Ran the orchestral programs for middle schools and high schools in Virginia, educating and directing students in grades 6-12.
- Taught multiple levels of piano and music in special education.
- Maintained instrument inventories, music libraries, attire inventories. and finances for all orchestra programs.
- Planned and executed fundraisers, concerts, events both local and longdistance, and small to large scale trips.
- Designed attire and marketing campaign tools to promote the programs
- Taught students both virtual and in-person simultaneously, and created digital content and concerts during the 2020-2021 year.
- Proficient in Microsoft and Google suites

#### EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER PROGRAM BACHELOR OF ARTS, MUSIC **EDUCATION** 

CareerFoundry Jan 2021 - Nov 2021 Crane School of Music, SUNY Potsdam 2011 - 2015